all righty guys welcome to another video and in this tutorial I want to show you
所有人都欢迎来到另一个视频 在本教程中，我想 告诉你
guys about the zip function Z IP now my guess is that if you've been programming
各位 关于zip功能 Z IP现在我的 猜测，如果你一直在编程
Python for like any decent amount of time you probably saw this a lot and
Python就像任何体面的数量一样 时间你可能看到这个了 很多 ，
it's kind of confusing to know exactly what it does just by looking at it the
确切地知道这有点令人困惑 它只是 看 它 做
very first time so I'll go ahead and show you guys a real basic example now
第一次， 所以我会继续 前进 现在告诉你们一个真实的基本例子
basically what we're going to do is we're going to have two lists of equal
基本上我们要做的是 我们将有两个相同的列表
lengths and we're going to zip them together or time together so we're going
长度 ，我们要拉链 在一起或时间在一起，所以我们要去
to return a final list of tuples so I'll make a really simple demonstration this
返回最后的元组列表，所以我会 做一个非常简单的演示
won't be anything useful but it'll be really easy to see what's going on so
不会有任何用处，但它会有用 真的很容易看出发生了什么
say that we have two lists of names Bucky and these are all first names Tom and Taylor now we have another list of
说我们有两个名单 Bucky和 这些都是汤姆的名字 和泰勒现在我们有另一个清单
equal lengths and this can be the last names so Bucky my last name is Roberts
等长 ，这可能是 最后一个 所以Bucky我的姓是Roberts
we'll say it's Tom Hanks and Taylor oh
我们会说汤姆汉克斯和泰勒 哦
my oh my pumpkin pie alright so I have two lists right here and obviously it
我的南瓜饼我好哦，所以我有 两个列表就在这里，显然它
would be really nice if we could tie these together somehow because in our
如果我们可以打平，那将是 非常好的 这些在一起， 因为在我们的
program basically we're always going to be using these together the first and
程序基本上我们总是会去 第一次 和 第一次使用这些
last name you always see them together in pretty much every computer program
姓氏，你总是看到他们在一起 在几乎所有的计算机程序中
say we're making a social network or something so what you can do instead of
说我们正在建立 社交网络或 东西，所以你可以做什么 ， 而不是
iterating through the entire thing in some kind of for loop with a counter and
迭代整个事物 某种带有计数器和for循环的循环
calling um like 0 1 2 every time that can get kind of messy so instead what you can do is zip them together so call
每次 都叫 0 1 2 可能会变得混乱 所以反而是什么 你可以做的就是将它们拉在一起然后打电话
the function zip and inside here is the parameters you toss in whatever list you
功能zip和里面这里是 参数您在任何 名单 折腾 你
want to zip together so this is pretty much saying ok take the first list which
我想拉链，所以这很漂亮 多说OK采取的第一个列表 ，它
is this and the last one and tie them together and store that in a final list
这是最后一个，并将它们捆绑在一起 一起并将其存储 在 最终列表中
of tuples called names so let's go ahead and take a look at names just so we can
称为名字的元组所以让我们继续吧 并且我们可以看看名字
visually see what exactly is going on so again I know that I just tied together
直观地看到究竟 发生了 什么 我知道我只是捆绑在一起
listen I'm just loop through them right now so it's kind
听我只是 现在循环通过它们，所以它是善良的
of pointless but again this is just a demonstration so for a be and names
毫无意义， 但这只是一个 为了一个 和名字的演示
print a B so let me just run through this and check this out
打印一个B所以让我来看看吧 这个，看看这个
Bucky Roberts Tom Hanks and Taylor Swift now like I said what this is actually
Bucky Roberts Tom Hanks和Taylor Swift 现在就像我 说的 那样
doing is making a list of tuples so it actually looks something like this
这样做是使元组的列表，以便它 实际上看起来 像这样
Bucky Roberts um let's copy this so it's going to look something like this
Bucky Roberts 嗯，让我们复制 这个吧 看起来像这样
Bucky Roberts Tom Hanks and Taylor Swift so again whenever we loop the room it's
Bucky Roberts Tom Hanks和Taylor Swift 所以，每当我们循环房间时，它就是这样
going to break them apart and you can access each individual element if you
打破他们，你可以 如果您 访问 每个元素
need to or keep them together in a nice zip list so again this example not very
需要或在一个不错的让他们在一起 zip列表所以再次这个例子 不是很好
good but now that we understand the basics of what a zip is what does it
好， 但现在我们明白了 拉链是什么的基础知识
function is and basically how it's constructed we're going to be seeing
功能是，基本上是如何 构建我们将会看到
this a lot whenever you want to actually do something with these items like
这很多，只要你想要实际 用这些东西做点什么
comparing numbers say that these were two numbers you can say okay if a is greater than B then safe a or maybe I
比较数字说这些 是 你可以说两个数字， 如果是的话 大于B 然后安全a或者我
don't know multiply the two numbers together and you're looking for the
不知道乘以这两个数字 在一起， 你正在寻找
result something you know a little more practical like that in a weird
结果你知道多一点 像一个奇怪的实用
real-world application so uh yeah there we go and it's videos only like four
现实世界的应用所以呃， 是的 我们去看它的视频 只有四个
minutes long so I went a little faster than actually that's it that's all the
几分钟，所以我 走得快 一点 实际上就是这就是全部
Python for this video but I do have a sort he tells since this video so short
这个视频的 Python， 但我有一个 他说，因为这段视频 太短了
and again totally unrelated Python um so you can move on to next soro but for
再次完全不相关的Python嗯所以 你可以继续前进到下一个soro但是
those who want a little entertainment this is something kind of funny that
那些想要一点娱乐的人 这有点好笑
Avenue I went to my mom's house last night because there's a hockey game and
大道我最后去了我妈妈的家 晚上， 因为有一个曲棍球 比赛和
my little cousin was over there and his mom is super strict like she only lets
我的小表弟 在那边和他的 妈妈是超级严格的，就像她只是让
him eat organic food and he's not allowed to drink soda or anything like
他吃有机食品， 但他不是 允许 喝苏打水或类似的东西
that so me and my sister in the silicon my little cousin were sent around the
这 使我和 我的妹妹硅 我的小表弟被 周围 的 发
dinner table and I always like to be like kind of goofy around kids just see how they react so my mom went to the UM
餐桌和我总是喜欢 就像孩子们看到的那种高飞一样 他们如何反应， 所以我的妈妈去了 密歇根大学
it was like it's it wasn't the regular stores like this Amish store we can get baked goods is she bought this little
它就像它 不是常规的 我们可以买到这样的Amish商店 烘焙食品是她买的这个小
loaf of bread it's like a little bit bigger than the size of a cell phone so
的面包 就好像一点点 比手机的大小还要大
I picked it up and I started I started talking to like I was talking to someone
我把它拿起来，我开始了 说话 就像我在和别人说话
and I'm like Hello completely serious and my sister she
我就像你好 完全认真 ，我姐姐她
just was like playing along with it exactly she didn't even smile or
就像是 和它一起玩 确切地说，她甚至没有微笑或
anything so now my little cousin is like looking at me like he's thinking about
所以现在我的 小 表弟 就像 看着我像他的思考
laughing but then he's like looking around he's like how come no one else is
笑，但后来他就像 在寻找 围绕他喜欢怎么就没有其他人
smiling is this guy like really talking to someone on this bread phone so uh so I'm like hello and I asked them to be
微笑是这个人真的在说话 这个面包手机上有人这么呃 我喜欢你好，我问过他们
quiet because I can't hear very good on my bread phone so I'm like oh it's my
安静， 因为 我听不到 很好 我的面包电话所以我喜欢哦， 这是 我的
doctor and I go oh the test results are in
医生和我去哦测试结果是 在
Oh what is it it's a yeast infection and then and then my sister just busts out
哦它是什么酵母感染和 然后，然后我妹妹 刚刚被淘汰出
laughing because she couldn't keep her I don't know she couldn't keep a straight
笑， 因为她 无法留住 她我 不知道她不能保持 直线
face anymore and then his mom she comes over if she starts flipping out because
面对了，然后他的妈妈来了 如果她 开始 翻身 ， 因为
like I said he's like she's like so straight-edged and I did she said you
就像我说 他就像她一样 我是 直截了当的 ，她说过你
can't talk to him about yeast infections and yeah yeah yeah but uh I don't know
不能和他谈论酵母菌感染 是的，是的，但是， 我不知道
like the story doesn't have a punch line or anything so that's as good as it gets
类似的故事没有一个妙语 或任何所以这是因为它 得到 良好
but I thought it was pretty funny and she was even more mad that me and my
但我觉得这很有趣 她对我和我更加生气
sister were laughs and when she was like trying to scold us or whatever but that
姐姐笑了，当她喜欢的时候 试图骂我们或其他什么，但那
is my yeast infection story so oh well thank you guys for watching now you know about syphilis and I will see you next
是我的酵母感染故事 哦哦 谢谢大家 现在看 你知道 关于梅毒， 我 接下来 会见到你
time
时间